themartingarrixshop.com 2019-09-24

# Privacy Policy– The Martin Garrix Shop

The Martin Garrix Shop Privacy Policy

 \-----

  **Privacy Policy**

STITCHED Global Production House B.V. ("we", “us”), are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.

This Privacy Policy (together with our General Terms and Conditions and any other documents referred to in it) describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase via the URL: https://shop.martingarrix.com/ (the “Webstore”). Please read the following carefully to understand our practices regarding your information and how we will treat it.

By visiting the Webstore you are accepting and consenting to the practices described in this policy (including as updated or amended from time to time). If, for any reason, you do not agree to the terms of this policy, please stop using the Webstore immediately.

This Webstore is operated by STITCHED Global Production House, registered at the Dutch Chamber of Commerce (Kamer van Koophandel), under number 69169543.

Our Address:

STITCHED Global Production House

Postjesweg 1 (room 1.30a)

1057 DT Amsterdam

The Netherlands

webshop@martingarrix.com

**PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT**

When you visit the Webstore, we automatically collect the following information:

  * Your internet browser and device type;
  * Your IP address;
  * Your time zone;
  * Some of the cookies that are installed on your device;
  * Information about the individual web pages or products that you view;
  * What websites or search terms referred you to the Webstore;
  * Information about how you interact with the Webstore.

We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information”.

We collect Device Information using the following technologies:

\- “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit http://www.allaboutcookies.org.

\- “Log files” track actions occurring on the Webstore, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.

\- “Web beacons”, “tags”, and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Webstore.

Additionally, when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Webstore, subscribe to our newsletter through the Webstore, or create an account through the Webstore, we collect certain information from you, including: 

  * Your first name and last name; 
  * Your billing address; 
  * Your shipping address; 
  * Payment information (including credit card numbers, bank account numbers); 
  * Your email address, 
  * Your phone number. 

We refer to this information as “Order Information”.

When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information, Order Information.

**HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**

We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Webstore (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to:

\- Communicate with you;

\- Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and

\- When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.

We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Webstore (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Webstore, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).

**SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above. We use Shopify to power our online store--you can read more about how Shopify uses your Personal Information here: https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy. We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Webstore -- you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/. You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout>. 

We use MailChimp as our email marketing automation platform. MailChimp will save your name and email address in a secure environment. MailChimp uses Cookies to gain insight into whether emails have been opened and read. 

Furthermore, we may share your Order Information with our logistics partners to fulfill and deliver your order.

Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.

**BEHAVIOURAL ADVERTISING**

As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.

You can opt out of targeted advertising by using the links below:

\- Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads

\- Google: https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous

\- Bing: https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads

Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: <http://optout.aboutads.info/>.

**COOKIES**

Here is a list of cookies that we use.

 _session_id, unique token, sessional, Allows Shopify to store information about your session (referrer, landing page, etc).

 _shopify_visit, no data held, Persistent for 30 minutes from the last visit, used by our website provider’s internal stats tracker to record the number of visits

 _shopify_uniq, no data held, expires midnight (relative to the visitor) of the next day, Counts the number of visits to a store by a single customer.

cart, unique token, persistent for 2 weeks, Stores information about the contents of your cart.

 _secure_session_id, unique token, sessional

 storefront_digest, unique token, indefinite If the shop has a password, this is used to determine if the current visitor has access.

**DO NOT TRACK**

Please note that we do not alter our Webstore’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.

**YOUR RIGHTS**

If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.

You have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority if you believe we may be processing your Personal Data in an incorrect way. You can find more information about how to lodge on the website of the Dutch Data Protection Authority: https://autoriteitpersoonsgegevens.nl/nl/contact-met-de-autoriteit-persoonsgegevens/tip-ons

Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Webstore), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.

**DATA RETENTION**

When you place an order through the Webstore, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to erase this information. In the case of an application for erasure, you will be informed by us within one month about the measures taken or the reasons for refusal. We may be required to store invoices containing your Order Information as long as the applicable law requires.

**SECURITY**

To protect your personal information, we take reasonable precautions and follow industry best practices to make sure it is not inappropriately lost, misused, accessed, disclosed, altered or destroyed.

If you provide us with your credit card information, the information is encrypted using secure socket layer technology (SSL) and stored with an AES-256 encryption.  Although no method of transmission over the Internet or electronic storage is 100% secure, we follow all PCI-DSS requirements and implement additional generally accepted industry standards.

**CHANGES**

We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.

**MINORS**

The Webstore is not intended for individuals under the age of 16 (sixteen).

**CONTACT US**

For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at webshop@martingarrix.com or by mail using the details provided below:

STITCHED Global Production House 

[Re: Privacy Compliance]

Postjesweg 1 (room 1.30a)

1057 DT Amsterdam

The Netherlands

Amsterdam, August 2018

\-----
